University of Connecticut, Board of Trustees Records 1987.0007
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
- Series I: Minutes, 1881-
  - pp. 8705 - 8716, 2004 November 17 (Box 112:, Folder 1037)
    - Handouts (Box 112:, Folder 1039)
  - pp. 8717 - 8733, 2005 February 3 (Box 112:, Folder 1040)
    - Attachments, 1987-0007/Series1/Box112:1041 (Box 112:, Folder 1041)
    - Handouts (Box 112:, Folder 1042)
  - Agenda, 2005 March 11 (Box 113, Folder 1043)
  - pp. 8734 - 8745, 2005 April 12 (Box 113:, Folder 1044)
    - Attachments, 1987-0007/Series1/Box113:1045 (Box 113:, Folder 1045)
    - Handouts (Box 112:, Folder 1046)
  - pp. 8746 - 8747, 2005 May 9 (Box 113:, Folder 1047)
  - pp. 8748 - 8759, 2005 June 1 (Box 113:, Folder 1048)
    - Attachments, 1987-0007/Series1/Box113:1049 (Box 113:, Folder 1049)
    - Handouts (Box 113:, Folder 1050)
  - pp. 8760 - 8770, 2005 June 21 (Box 112:, Folder 1051)
    - Handouts (Box 113:, Folder 1052)
    - Attachments, June 21, 2005; 1987-0007/Series1/Box113/6-21-2005Attachments
  - pp. -, 2005 August 2 (Box 113:, Folder 1053)
    - Attachments, August 2, 2005; 1987-0007/Series1/Box113/8/2/2005Attachments (Box 113:, Folder 1054)
  - pp. 8785 - 8798, 2005 September 20 (Box 113:, Folder 1055)
    - Attachments, September 20, 2005; 1987-0007/Series1/Box113/9-20-2005Attachments (Box 113:, Folder 1056)
    - Handouts (Box 113:, Folder 1057)
  - pp. 8799 - 8815, 2005 November 15 (Box 113:, Folder 1058)
    - Attachments, November 15, 2005; 1987-0007/Series1/Box114:11-15-2005Attachments (Box 113:, Folder 1059)
    - Handouts (Box 114:, Folder 1060)
  - pp. 8816-8834, 2006 January 31 (Box 114:, Folder 1061)
    - Attachments, January 31, 2006; 1987-0007/Series1/Box114/1-31-2006Attachments (Box-folder 114:1-31-2006Attachments, Box 114:, Folder 1062)
  - pp. 8835-8849, 2006 March 1 (Box 114:, Folder 1063)
    - Attachments, March 1, 2006; 1987-0007/Series1/Box114/3-1-2006Attachments (Box 114:, Folder 1064)
    - pp. 8850-8868, 2006 April 11 (Box 114:, Folder 1065)
    - Attachments, April 11, 2006; 1987-0007/Series1/Box114:4-11-2006Attachments (Box 114:, Folder 1066)
    - Fiancial Report (Box 114:, Folder 1067)
    - Storrs Campus Master Plan 2006 (Box 114:, Folder 1068)
  - pp. 8869-8913, 2006 May 12 - 2006 September 26 (Box 115)
    - Attachments, May 15, 2006; 1987-0007/Series1/5-15-2006Attachments
    - Attachments, June 20, 2006; 1987-0007/Series1/Box115:6-20-2006
    - Attachments, September 26, 2006; 1987-0007/Series1/115:9-26-2006Attachments (Box 115)
  - pp. 8914-8963, 2006 November 14 - 2007 March 13 (Box 116)
    - Attachments, November 14, 2006; 1987-0007/Series1/Box116:11-14-2006Attachments
    - Attachments, January 30, 2007; 1987-0007/Series1/Box116:1-30-2007Attachments
    - Attachments, March 13, 2007; 1987-0007/Series1/Box116:3-13-2007Attachments
  - pp. 8964-9030, 2007 April 10 - 2007 September 25 (Box 117)
    - Attachments, April 10, 2007; 1987-0007/Series1/Box117/4-10-2007Attachments
    - Attachments, June 19, 2007; 1987-0007/Series1/Box117:6-19-2007Attachments
    - Attachments, August 1, 2007; 1987-0007/Series1/Box117:8-1-2007Attachments
    - Attachments, September 25, 2007; 1987-007/Series1/Box117:9-25-2007Attachments
  - pp. 9031-, 2007 December 4 - 2008 September 23 (Box 118)
    - Attachments, September 23, 2008; 1987-0007/Series1/Box119:9-23-2008Attachments
    - Attachments, 2007 December 4; 1987.007/Series 1/Box 118:12-4-2007 Attachments
    - Attachments, 2008 January 22; 1987.0007/Series1/Box 118:01-22-2008
    - Attachments, 2008 February 27; 1987.0007/Series 1/Box 118:02-27-2008 Attachments
    - Attachments, April 15, 2008; 1987.007/Series1/Box118:04-15-2008
    - Attachments, 2008 June 24; 1987.0007/Series 1/Box 118:06-24-2008 Attachments
  - Minutes, 2008 November 18 - 2009 June 23
    - Attachments, 2008 November 18; 1987.0007/Series 1/Box 120:11-18-2008 Attachments
- Series II: Correspondence and Supporting materials, 1970-1992
  - 1970-1979 (Box 1)
  - 1979-1985 (Box 2)
  - 1990-1992 (Box 3)
  - 1992 (Box 4)
- Series III: Subject Files, undated, 1970-1985
  - Academy for Educational Development: Panel Report (Box 22)
  - Activities
  - Ad Hoc Committee on Planning
  - Ad Hoc Committee to Review Administrative Salary Schedules, (2 folders)
  - Admissions
  - Agenda
  - Agricultural publications
  - Alumni
  - Apartments: rental increases
  - Appeals and Grievances
    - Epstein
    - Holland
    - Kardestuncer
    - Lieberman
    - McMeekin
    - Multer
    - Scholar v. Perruccio
    - Simmons, (2 folders)
    - Venham, (2 folders)
  - Applications for Assistant to the Executive Secretary, (2 folders)
  - Articles
  - Blue Ribbon Commission
  - Board of Higher Education, 1976-1978
  - Board of Higher Education, 1979-1981
  - Board of Higher Education Reports
  - Branford House Dinner, 1983 December 3
  - Brunch, President's Residence, 1983 October 15
  - Budget
  - Budget: President's Office
  - Burns Report, 1970
  - Cabinet Retreat, President's Residence, 1984 November 5 - 6
  - Canadian Consul Dinner, President's Residence, 1984 November 18
  - Central Naugatuck Valley Region Higher Education Center
  - Collective Bargaining Agreement, 1979 July 1 - 1981 June 30
  - Committee on Archival Policy, 1974-1975
  - Committee to Study Food Service, 1975
  - Committee to Study Recommendations on Admissions and Enrollment Report, 1974
  - Community Relations Committee, 1979-1981; (2 folders)
  - Community Relations Committee, 1982
  - Council on Human Rights and Opportunities Conferences and Institutions Conference and Providence Game, 1981 February 21
  - Connecticut Law Review, 1983
  - Correspondence, David L. Kimball and Michigan State University
  - Council of Presidents, Meetings, 1983 June 13 - 15
  - Development
  - Dialogue Dinner, 1984 January 4
  - Dining Hall Committee, 1975
  - Director of Public Affairs
    - Advertising
    - Budget (Box 23)
    - Ideas
    - Resumes
  - D'Oliveira clippings, (2 folders)
  - Editorial Projects for Education, 15-Minute Report
  - E.O. Smith High School
  - Etherington Report
  - Executive Assistant to the President, David L. Kimball, (2 folders)
  - Federation of Students and Service Organizations, Minutes
  - Filer Committee
  - Government Relations
  - Health Center Commencement, 1982
  - Health Center Development
  - Health Center Public Information
  - Honorary Degree Dinner, 1984 May 20
  - Housing for Trustees
  - Housing policy
  - Insignia: use
  - Internal budget
  - Laws and by-laws
  - Legislative reception, Governor's Mansion, 1982 March 23
  - Library Dedication, 1984 May 18
  - Mendez, Nicanor Costa Faculty-Alumni Reception
  - Metanoia
  - Minutes, 1985
  - Miscellaneous, 1975-1985; (2 folders)
  - Mortar Board
  - New England Land-Grant Universities: Subdegree Student Exchange Program
  - Non-Credit Program
  - Northwood Apartments Meeting, 1984 May 11
  - Off-Campus Programs
  - On the Road with Charles Kuralt, 1983 August 16
  - Organization Charts
  - Personnel
  - Photo
  - Photo Lab Phi Beta Kappa, 1984 October 17
  - Public Affairs, Advertising
  - Public Relations News
  - Publications Review Committee, 1975
  - Representation Allowance, 1978-1979
  - Retreat, 1979 November 19
  - Scranton Report, 1970
  - 60 Minutes, 1983 March 6
  - Smeal, Eleanor Dinner, 1985 April 4
  - Speakers
  - Stamford Branch Expansion Report, 1979 January
  - Standing Advisory Committee, Board of Governors
  - Student Employment
  - Student Health and Accident Insurance Committee, 1975
  - Student organizations
  - Student Trustee candidates
  - Student Trustee election, 1975
  - Student Trustee election, 1976-1980; (5 folders) (Box 24)
  - Student Trustee Election Committee
    - Signed petitions
    - Special election, Bill Finch, 1978
    - Vouchers
  - Student Trustee election petitions
  - Study of the Cost of Instruction and Faculty Performance and Accountability, 1973
  - Torrington Branch: Grover, (3 folders)
  - Torrington Branch: Petitions, 1983
  - Trustee Dinner, 1981 December 4
  - Trustee information, (2 folders)
  - Tuition, S.B. 842
  - TV commercials
  - UConn PIRG
  - University Foundation
  - Imoversotu Senate Executive Committee, 1984-1985
  - Vice President, Finance and Administration: Search, 1984
  - Vice Presidential Searches
- Series IV: Committee Files, undated, 1977-1992
  - Budget and Finance Committee
    - Finance Committee Minutes, 1972-1975; (8 folders) (Box 23)
    - Finance Committee Minutes, 1973-1974 (Box 30)
    - Finance Committee Minutes, 1974-1975 (Box 31)
    - Budget and Finance Committee Minutes, 1977-1978 (Box 31)
    - Budget and Finance Committee materials, 1979-1980 (Box 29)
  - Health Affairs
    - Health Affairs Committee Minutes
      - 1977 September - 1978 June
      - 1978 July - 1979 September (Box 25)
      - 1979 October - 1981 December
      - 1981 February - 1983 September
    - Health Affairs-Hospital Committee Minutes
      - 1977 September - 1978 October
      - 1979 October - 1980 October
      - 1980 November - 1981 November
      - 1982 April - November
      - 1983 March - October
    - University Hospital Board of Trustees
      - 1975 February - 1976 May
      - 1976 June - 1980 July
  - Institutional Policy Committee
    - 1976 May 14 - 1988 September 15
    - 1988 October 14 - 1992 July 10
  - Buildings, Grounds and Environment Committee, 1998-2011
    History
    Formerly known as the Master Plan Advisory Committee. Files were transferred by Dr. Karla Fox.
    Scope and Contents
    [Subjects include: Building and grounds, environmental policy, parking and transportation, campus safety, environmental conservation, Human rights, material sciences, School of Business, School of Engineering, NCAA, UConn Academic Task Force.]
    - Administrative records, clippings, correspondence, illustrations, maps, notes, 1999, 2000-2001, 2003-2005 (Box 2011-0020_1)
    - Administrative records, correspondence, maps, notes, publications, 2004-2005 (Box 2011-0020_2)
    - Administrative records, correspondence, maps, notes, photographs, 1997, 2005-2006 (Box 2011-0020_3)
    - Administrative records, correspondence, maps, notes, photographs, 2003-2009 (Box 2011-0020_4)
    - Administrative records, clippings, correspondence, financial records, fliers, illustrations, maps, notes, optical disks (2), photographs, tapes, 1999, 2000-2003, 2005-2006 (Box 2011-0020_5)
    - Administrative records, correspondence, 1995-1999, 2000-2003 (Box 2011-0020_6)
    - Administrative records, clippings, correspondence, fliers, maps, notes, photographs, 1998-2000 (Box 2011-0020_7)
    - Administrative records, clippings, correspondence, financial records, fliers, maps, notes, 1998-1999, 2000-2009 (Box 2011-0020_8)
    - Administrative records, optical disks (1), 2008-2009 (Box 2011-0020_9)
    - Administrative record, notes, 2003-2007 (Box 2011-0020_10)
    - Administrative records, clippings, correspondence, financial records, notes, 2002-2003, 2005-2009 (Box 2011-0020_11)
    - Administrative records, correspondence, maps, 2009-2011 (Box 2011-0020_12)
- Series V: Biographies and Plans, undated, 1936-1972
  - Biographies
    - Ackerly, Barbara
    - Allie, John
    - Altschuler, Stephen
    - Andersen, Kenneth
    - Ash, Albert
    - Bacchus, Wilfred
    - Bailey, Barbara
    - Barry, Philip
    - Battles, Richard (Rev.)
    - Benton, William
    - Bishop, Merlin
    - Blum, John
    - Booth, Marcella
    - Bradlaw, Elizabeth
    - Brisco, Martha
    - Brown, George
    - Brown, Otha, (2 folders)
    - Budds, John (Box 26)
    - Bunch, John
    - Burns, Joseph
    - Cafero, Donald
    - Caisse, Frank X.
    - Canzonetti, Andrew, (3 folders)
    - Carlson, Adolf
    - Carter, Arthur
    - Castaldi, Cosmo
    - Catanese, Richard
    - Clark, Lillian
    - Cobb, Dorothy
    - Collins, Mark
    - Crisco, Joseph
    - Cunningham, John
    - D'Oliveria, Arthur
    - Daniels, Willard
    - Dehlinger, Peter
    - Donen, Steven
    - Donohue, Alphonsus
    - Dowling, Kevin
    - Early, Edward
    - Emmert, Fred
    - Ferrandino, Vincent
    - Finch, William
    - Flynn, John T.
    - Gall, Galvin
    - Galotti, Joseph
    - Gamble, Richard
    - Germain, Carel B.
    - Grant, Donald
    - Greene, John
    - Haskew, Derek
    - Herdon, John J.
    - Hill, George
    - Horton, Barnaby
    - Isidro-Cloudas, Peter
    - Jeffers, Albert
    - Jones, Betty
    - Jacobs, Donald
    - Johnson, Geoffrey
    - Johnson, James
    - Jorgensen, Norma
    - Kahn, Harris
    - Kammer, Harold J.
    - Keith, Jean L.
    - Kemmerr, Howard
    - Kirk, Irene
    - Kleban, Albert
    - Kottke, Marvin
    - Kozloski, Walter
    - Krough, Leonard
    - Kubric, Joseph
    - Lawrence, Gerald M.D.
    - Leone, Daniel
    - Liberman, Alvin
    - Liberman, Isabelle
    - Lonergan, Jean
    - Lowney, Jeremiah
    - Lupton, John
    - Macdonald, John
    - Marcus, Walter
    - Marlin, Bernard
    - Mazcy, Ellis
    - McCormick, Joseph
    - Micocci, Rhoda
    - Mika, Thomas
    - Moeller, Carl
    - Nadolny, Susan
    - Nielsen, Carl
    - Noether, Emiliana P.
    - O'Neil, Governor William
    - Opinsky, Jack
    - Parker, James
    - Perovitch, Milosh
    - Phillips, Richard
    - Piggott, Charlotte
    - Raducha, Sally
    - Ray, Ryan
    - Rich, Frank, (2 folders)
    - Richter, Roland
    - Roach, Jack
    - Rogers, Neal
    - Rollins, Calvin
    - Ross, Calvin
    - Rossi, Theodore
    - Rotter, Julian
    - Sadow, Helen (Box 27)
    - Samuelson, Henry
    - Sanders, William
    - Sevarino, Joann
    - Shedd, Mark
    - Shippee, Lester
    - Singleton, Robert
    - Smith, Virginia
    - Stanley, Emily
    - Stephenson, Richard
    - Stewart, Robert
    - Striker, Ardelle
    - Stroh, Charles
    - Tasker, Gordon
    - Taylor, Michael
    - Taylor, Robert
    - Tirozzi, Gerald
    - Tlustokowicz, Julius
    - Turner, Nathalie
    - Twardy, Stanel
    - Ullmar, Joyce
    - Ushery, David
    - Walsh, Thomas
    - Waller, W. DeHomer
    - Wandersee, Edward P.
    - Waterman, H. Earl
    - Weiker, Lowell
    - Whinfield, Richard
    - Wiggins, Robert
    - Wilbur, George
    - White, Francis
  - Statement by BOT of the Minimum Needs of the Connecticut State College, 1936
  - Plans of BOT for post-war development of UConn, 1945 January (Box 28)
  - A Study of the Problems Confronting Higher Education in Connecticut, 1957 January
  - Capital Building Program- Report to BOT, 1972 September; (2 folders)
  - Trustee Policy Book, (5 folders)
- Series VI: 2012 Transfer, 1995-1998
  - Meeting minutes, agenda, handouts, files and documents (v. 177-119), 1997 (Box 2012-0080_3)
  - Meeting minutes, agenda, handouts, files and documents (v. 120-122), 1998 (Box 2012-0080_4)
  - Meeting minutes, agenda, handouts, files and documents, 1999 (Box 2012-0090_V)
  - Revisions and handouts from meetings (no minutes), 2011 (Box 2012-0090_2011)
  - Transfer I, 1995 (Box 2012_1)
  - Transfer II, 1996 (Box 2012_2)
- Series VII: Honorary Degrees, 1991-1997
  - Administrative records, correspondence, 1991-1997 (Box 120)
    Scope and Content Note
    [Subjects include: the documentation for conferral of honorary degrees.]
- Series VIII: 2015 tranfer, 1996-2001
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, 2010-2015 (Box 2015.0038_1)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, 1998-2015 (Box 2015.0038_2)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, 2006-2015 (Box 2015.0038_3)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, 1998-2001 (Box 2015.0038_4)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, 1985-2014 (Box 2015.0038_5)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, Handouts, Administrative papers, 2009-2015 (Box 2015-0039_1, Box 2015-0039_2)
    Administrative records in the from of meeting minutes, handouts, agendas, limited financial information
    The Special Workshop Facilities and Capital Planning binder containing the planning concerned with the creation of the UCONN Health Center: Information and Technologies Strategic Plan Campus and Facilities Master Plan Capital Budget Process UCONN21 Process
    Joint Audit and Compliance Committee meeting records from 2009 to 2015 Information concerning financial records for different organizations and departments of UCONN
    Board of Trustees meeting minutes, agendas and handouts from June 2014 to October 2014
  - Agenda, handouts, action items (v. 134-148), 2014 January 29 - 2014 December 29 (Box 2015-0109_1)
- Series IX: 2016 Transfer, 2015 (Box 2016_0010_1)
  Agenda, Minutes and handouts for 2015